Look.
Over there.
Okay.
Shiya.
To be honest,
do you think the big data social intelligent algorithm I made
really has any meaning to exist?
Why are you asking this all of a sudden?
I always thought in the past
that life could not be changed,
and a person's life
was like a string of precise data.
All I needed to do
was extract this data
and hand it over to the intelligent algorithm
to help people
increase the probability of meeting their destined ones.
But now I regret it.
I actually feel
that I'd rather believe
the clock of fate has never stopped.
However,
your algorithm has a bug.
I've been wanting to tell you.
What are you 'ah'-ing about?
Don't question my professionalism
as a data maintenance engineer.
Your system...
How is that possible?
There's no way the system I built has a problem.
Why couldn't the system you built have a problem?
Listen to me.
The system I built has been tested many times.
It doesn't...
It's burnt.
Look at this.
No, don't change the subject.
How could the system I built have a bug?
I always feel
that everyone in this universe
is a line of code,
and even time itself is.
Do you think so?
Don't get me wrong.
I just thought
it might be more comfortable leaning on me.
Shiya.
Pei Song.
Where are you?
Over there.
Shiya.
Brother.
I finally found you.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's nothing.
Let's go back first.
As long as we found them.
Slow down.
We're going back.
Check the dashcam of that SUV.
I suspect someone tampered with it.
Okay.
This time,
I will definitely investigate thoroughly.
I won't let Shiya die again.
The dashcam is gone.
Yes, Mr. Pei.
I got to the parking lot as soon as possible,
and the dashcam was already gone.
Mr. Pei.
Could it have been thrown out during the crash
and fell into the mountains?
Impossible.
My dashcam was reinforced.
Unless someone took it down manually.
At first I only suspected,
but now I'm almost certain.
Someone tampered with my car.
Good thing I had a backup plan.
I installed tracking software
on the dashcam.
Mr. Pei.
You installed tracking software on the dashcam?
Do you want me to notify the police?
Mr. Pei.
I'll handle this myself.
You can go back to work.
Did you need me for something?
Why?
Why what?
Why did you take the dashcam?
I don't know what you mean.
I'll go cook for you.
What do you want to eat?
Give me the dashcam.
Are you hiding something from me?
Or do you know who the killer is?
What does he have to do with you?
There are some things you don't need to know.
Why don't I need to know?
On this trip,
first there was a problem with the rope,
and then the car.
I don't want to just watch you
die in front of me.
You are my wife.
I am your husband.
It is my duty and obligation to protect you.
Not for long.
What are you doing?
Let me go.
Last time,
the person who killed you also came on a motorcycle.
Last time?
You were reborn.
How do you know?
What exactly happened last time?
Don't talk for now.
Every time you die in front of me...
I am always reborn.
I don't know how many more times this will happen.
But this time,
I won't let anyone hurt you again.
Actually,
I know you're reborn.
What did you say?
You said it before when you were drunk.
Right after we got married.
Right after we got married?
Are you willing to believe me?